(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
雪花ラミィ 2nd Anniversary Live!!! Fleur
Yukihana Lamy 2nd Anniversary Live!!! Fleur
好きになって
Fall in love with me
もっと私を見て
Look at me more
もっと恩返しは
Even more gratitude,
愛のこもった投げキッスで
with a love-filled blown kiss!
気のせいじゃない 目が合ってるよ
It's not your imagination, our eyes are meeting
ハートぶち抜いて
Shoot through your heart
恋しちゃってください
Please fall in love with me
やれること何でもします
I'll do anything I can
NGなしで
With no NGs
体当たり調査
A full-on investigation
ネットで見つけたアンチのコメ
An anti's comment I found online
不細工なのはわかってるし
I know I'm not that pretty
でも大丈夫 ここに立てば
But it's okay, if I stand here,
みんながいる
everyone is here
好きになって
Fall in love with me
もっと！
MORE!
私を見て
Look at me
もっと！
MORE!
恩返しは 愛のこもった投げキッスで
Gratitude with a love-filled blown kiss!
虜にする
I'll captivate you
もっと！
MORE!
夢を見せる
I'll show you a dream
もっと！
MORE!
楽しんでって 愛のこもったスペシャルナイト ファンサしちゃうぞ
Have fun! In this love-filled special night, I'll give you fan service!
お手紙も書いてください
Please write me letters too
何度も読んで 宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and cherish them as treasures
スキャンダル まだ早いけど
A scandal, it's too early for that
裏切りません
But I won't betray you
宣言しときます
I'll declare it now
嫉妬や嫌がらせには負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment
不細工なの実力で勝ってやる
I'll win with my skills despite not being pretty
だから辞めない 負けず嫌い
So I won't quit, I hate to lose
私はいる
I am here
拳上げて
Raise your fists
もっと！
MORE!
汗をかいて
Work up a sweat
もっと！
MORE!
恩返しは 愛のこもった投げキッスで
Gratitude with a love-filled blown kiss!
最高潮に
To the climax
もっと！
MORE!
まだまだねぇ
Not yet, okay?
もっと！
MORE!
受け止めてね 愛のこもったわがままソング ファンサしちゃうぞ
Please accept it, this love-filled selfish song. I'll give you fan service!
あー 終わりが近づく
Ah, the end is near
寂しいね 楽しくて 泣きそうだよ
It's lonely, I'm so happy I'm about to cry
次も 次も また会えるよね
Next time, and the time after, we'll meet again, right?
約束！
Promise!
優しさに溢れている言葉も
Words overflowing with kindness,
心ない誰かの言葉さえも
and even heartless words from someone,
必要なんだ 必要なんだ
I need them, I need them
強くなろう
I'll become stronger
好きに叫んで
Shout as much as you like
もっと！
MORE!
楽しんじゃえ
Just have fun
もっと！
MORE!
忘れないで 特別な日になりますように
Don't forget, I hope this becomes a special day
共に歌おう ずっと
Let's sing together, forever
共に歩もう ずっと
Let's walk together, forever
合言葉は とびっきりの L・O・V・E ファンサしちゃうぞ
The password is a special L-O-V-E. I'll give you fan service!
もっと！
More!
私を見て
Look at me
もっと！
More!
恩返しは
Returning the favor
愛のこもった「大好き」で
With an 'I love you' filled with love
Fooo!!
もっと！
More!
夢を見せる
I'll show you dreams
もっと！
More!
楽しんでって
Have fun
愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
It's a special night filled with love
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm gonna give you some fan service
ハイ！
Hi!
オイ！
Oi!
最高！俺の...俺のお姫様！あーーーー！
The best! My... my princess! Aaaa!
はい、ということで、始まりましたー！
Alright, and so, it has begun!
イエーイ！
Yay!
えーこちら雪花ラミィ 2nd Anniversary Live!!! "Fleur"
So, this is Yukihana Lamy 2nd Anniversary Live!!! "Fleur".
ということで、一曲目はファンサをお届けしました。
And for the first song, I performed "Fansa".
みんな見てくれたー？
Did everyone see it?
えー掛け声はですね、
For the calls,
同期のポルカと、ししろんと、ねねにお願いしました。
I asked my gen mates Polka, Shishiron, and Nene.
ポルカにね、あの自由な感じで、好きな感じでやっていいよって言ったらね
I told Polka she could do it freely, however she liked,
あんなもう凄いことになってました。
and it turned into something amazing.
凄いポルカらしくて良かったなと思います。三人ともありがとう！
It was very Polka-like and I think it was great. Thank you to the three of you!
これからまたね、その三人の周年記念もあるので、みんなでお祝いしていきましょう。
The three of them also have their anniversary celebrations coming up, so let's all celebrate together.
ということで、本日のタグ、こちら！
So, today's tag is this!
#雪花ラミィ2周年LIVE こちらでね、たくさん呟いていただければと思います。
#YukihanaLamy2ndAnnivLive. I hope you'll tweet a lot using this.
なんと、今日は初めてのゲストなしのラミィ一人でのライブです。
Believe it or not, today is my first solo live with no guests.
初めての一人でのライブになってます。
It's my first live by myself.
普段はね、あのゲストの先輩とか同期とか yonde yatteru n desu kedo
Usually, I invite seniors or gen mates as guests,
今日は2周年ということで、かっこいいラミィを見せたり、可愛いラミィを見せたり、
but since it's my 2nd anniversary, I want to show everyone a cool Lamy, a cute Lamy,
いろんなラミィをみんなに見せていけたらいいなと思っております。
and all different sides of Lamy to everyone.
そして、ライブの途中では、なんとね、
And during the live, there will also be,
100万人記念のちょっと前から匂わせてた重大な発表もありますので。
a major announcement that I've been hinting at since a bit before the 1 million milestone.
水族館コラボのちょっと詳しいお知らせがありますので、
There's more detailed news about the aquarium collaboration,
皆さんぜひぜひ、あの最後まで見逃しのないようにお願いします。
so everyone, please make sure not to miss anything until the end.
ということでね、じゃあ次に歌う曲なんですけど、
And so, the next song I'm going to sing is...
1曲目はね、アイドル曲って感じで歌ったんですけど、
The first song was very idol-like,
2曲目はね、こんな感じの...じゃじゃーん！
but the second one is like this... Ta-da!
この椅子は、何でしょう。ちょっと、なんかかっこいい感じの椅子が出てきましたけど。
What is this chair? A somewhat cool-looking chair has appeared.
ラミィも、いつものお酒ばっかり飲んでるラミィじゃなく、
Lamy isn't just the usual Lamy who's always drinking alcohol,
ちょっとね、かっこいいラミィをみんなに見せていこうかなと思っておりますよ。
I'm going to show everyone a bit of a cool Lamy.
それでは皆さん聞いてください。かっこいいラミィも見てね。
Now everyone, please listen. Watch the cool Lamy too.
KING
幽閉利口 逝く前に
Imprisoned cleverness, before passing away
ユーヘイ利口に難儀ダーリン
Imprisoned cleverly, in trouble darling
幽閉ストップ 知ってないし
Imprisoned stop, I didn't know
勘弁しといてなんて惨め
"Give me a break," how miserable
ひとさま願えば 欠かせぬワイロ
If you wish for others, a bribe is essential
誰もが願えど 無きもの強請
Everyone wishes, but asking for the impossible
人足先に 始めてたのラッシュ
Getting a head start, the rush began
先が見えない ヴァージンオプション
No end in sight, a virgin option
無いのあなたにお願いひとつ
I've got a single request for you
相も変わらず おまけに割り割り
Unchanged as always, and a split to boot
無いのあなたにお願いひとつ
I've got a single request for you
張り詰めた思い込め
With all my feelings held tight
Left side Right side 歯をむき出して
Left side Right side, baring your teeth
パッパッパッ 照れくさいね
Pa pa pa, it's embarrassing
Left side Right side 牙をむき出して
Left side Right side, baring your fangs
パッパッパッ
Pa pa pa
You are KING
全部消えていく
Everything's disappearing
無様に死ねる
I can die unsightly
身構えもなく鳴ってる
Sounding without a guard
ラ・ラ・ラ・ラ・ラッタッタ
La-la-la-la-ratatata
嫌い嫌いの最期を留め
Putting an end to the "hate, hate"
毎度新たにお願い一つ
One request, new every time
相も変わらずピックアップのワニワニ
Unchanged as ever, pickup's wani-wani
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
Nothing for you, one request
張り詰めた思い込め
With intense feelings...
Left side, Right side
歯を剥き出して　パッパッパ
Baring your teeth, pa-pa-pa
邪魔くさいね
What a nuisance
Left side, Right side
歯を突き出して　パッパッパ
Thrust out your teeth, pa-pa-pa
You are KING
名前のない怪物
作詞・作曲: ryo (supercell)
Monster without a Name
Lyrics & Composition: ryo (supercell)
震えてるわ　寒気したみたい
I'm shivering, as if I've caught a chill
絵画の表で　上手く笑えなくて
On the surface of the painting, unable to smile well
霧に煙る街
A town smoking in the mist
浮かぶ赤い月
A floating red moon
ほら見て私を
Look, look at me
目をそらさないで
Don't look away
黒い鉄格子の中で私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born inside black iron bars
悪意の代償願うがままにお前に
A price for malice, just as I wish for you
さあ　喰らえ正義を
Now, devour justice
壊して　壊される前に
Break it before you're broken
因果の代償払い
Paying the price of karma
共に行こう　名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster without a name
耳鳴りがしてる　鉄条うるさくて
My ears are ringing, the iron wires are so loud
思い出せないの　あの日の旋律
I can't remember the melody of that day
雨はまばら　まだ何も見えないの
The rain is sparse, I still can see nothing
ほら見て　こんなに大きくなったの
Look, look how big it's become
黒い雨降らせこの空　私は望まないもの
Let black rain fall from this sky, I am something unwanted
ひび割れた音色で愛す　同罪の傍観者たちに
Loving with a cracked tone, to the bystanders of the same crime
さあ今　奮え正義を
Now, brandish justice
消せない傷抱きしめて
Embracing the wounds that can't be erased
この体を受け入れ
Accept this body
共に行こう　名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster without a name
ああ...
Ah...
神は告げる
God proclaims
真の世界を
The true world
黒い鉄格子の中で私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born inside black iron bars
正義を壊して 壊される前に
Destroying justice before being destroyed
因果の代償を払い
Paying the price of causality
報いよ 名もなき怪物
Take your reward, nameless monster
黒い雨 降らせこの空
Let the black rain fall from this sky
私は 望まれないもの
I am something unwanted
ひび割れたノイズを吐き出し
Spitting out cracked noise
統制の崩壊した街に
Into the city where control has collapsed
さあいま 震え正義を
Now, tremble, justice
消さない 清浄抱きしめて
Don't extinguish it, embrace the purity
この体を 受け入れ
Accept this body
共に行こう 名前のない
Let's go together, nameless...
怪物
...monster
はい！
Yes!
ということで、えー、聴いていただきましたのは
So, the songs you just heard were...
『KING』そして『名前のない怪物』でした！
...'KING' and 'Namae no nai kaibutsu'!
いや、あの、実はですね、この2曲
Actually, these two songs...
すごく歌のリクエストが多かった曲なんですよ。
...were highly requested by everyone.
ま、ちょっとね、今回ラミィが
So this time, Lamy...
ちょっとこの何て言うんですかね
...tried to, how should I say...
なんかこうセクシーなKINGを目指してみたのと
...aim for a sexy 'KING'...
名前のない怪物ではね、ちょっとこう
...and for 'Namae no nai kaibutsu'...
カッコいい感じの怪物を目指してみました。
...tried to aim for a cool monster.
どうだったでしょうか、みんな？
How was it, everyone?
どう？うまくできてたかな？
How was it? Did I do well?
名前のない怪物がね、もうすごい
For 'Namae no nai kaibutsu'...
あの、息継ぎができなくて
...it was hard to find a place to breathe.
もうすごい大変だったんだけど、頑張りました！
It was so tough, but I did my best!
後でね、みんなの感想を見るの
I'm looking forward to reading...
楽しみにしてます。
...your comments later.
ふぅ、やっぱりね、一人で歌って踊ってっていうのはね
Whew, singing and dancing alone...
なかなか大変ですね。
...is quite tough, isn't it?
いや、まだまだね、これからもどんどん続いていくので
But it's not over yet, there's more to come!
ラミィも頑張ってね、次の曲行きますよ。
So I'll do my best. Let's move on to the next song.
次は、ま、ちょっと激しめの
Next... since I just sang two...
カッコいい曲を2曲歌ったので
...intense, cool songs...
次はちょっと、まあしっとりめな感じ？
...next is a bit more... mellow?
だけどちょっとカッコいい感じみたいな曲をね
But still with a cool vibe.
聴いてもらおうかなと思います。
I'd like you to hear it.
あの、みんなもきっと知ってる
It's a song that you all probably know...
歌ってみたでも出したあの曲です！
...one that I also did a cover of!
じゃあ、頑張ろう。頑張ります！
Okay, here goes. I'll do my best!
あ、ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って！
Oh, wait a second, wait!
何なに？急に光が！
What? Suddenly a light!
あー何？急に何？
Ah, what? Suddenly, what?
わあ、眩しい！
Whoa, so bright!
ああ、何も言ってないのに勝手に衣装チェンジした！
Ah, I didn't say anything but it's changing my costume!
いや、これはね、早く歌いなさいってことかな？
I guess this means 'Hurry up and sing'?
だと思うので、じゃあね、ちょっと衣装チェンジをしたところで
Since I've changed my costume...
歌っていきたいと思います！
...I'd like to start singing!
それでは皆さん、聴いてください。
Now everyone, please listen.
フォニイ
作詞・作曲：ツミキ
Phony
Lyrics & Music: Tsumiki
この世で造花より綺麗な花はない
In this world, no flowers are more beautiful than artificial ones
何故ならば全ては嘘で出来ている
Because everything is made of lies
Antipathy world
Lul-la, lul-la, lullaby
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を突いて
The rain of despair pokes at my umbrella
湿らす前髪と心のリズム
Dampening my bangs and my heart's rhythm
わずらわしいわ
It's so annoying
いつしか言の葉は疾うに枯れきって
Before I knew it, the leaves of words had already withered
事の実方に触れている
Touching the way things really are
鏡に映り嘘描いて
Drawing lies reflected in the mirror
自らを見失った迷彩
Camouflage that has lost sight of itself
パッパラパッパララパ
Pap-para, pap-para-ra-pa
謎々かぞえて遊びましょう
Let's play by counting riddles
タッタラタッタララタ
Tat-tara, tat-tara-ra-ta
何故何故ここで踊ってるでしょう
Why, oh why, are you dancing here?
簡単なことも解からないわ
I don't even understand simple things
あたしって何だっけ
Who was I again?
それすら夜の手法にほだされて
Even that is tamed by the night's methods
愛のように
Like love...
泣いた
...I cried
さよならも言えぬまま泣いた
I cried without being able to say goodbye
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, Phony, Phony
嘘に絡まっているあたしはフォニイ
Entangled in lies, I am a phony
Antipathy world
いつしか空の音がいやになり合って
Before I knew it, the sound of the sky became unpleasant
色の眼がなあと解いている
And I'm unraveling the eyes of color
あたしを書いて
Write me down
鏡に映るあたしを書いて
Write down the "me" reflected in the mirror
誰しもが身間違ったフェイク
Everyone is a mistaken fake
如何して 愛なんてものに群がり
Why do we flock to things like love
ズレを欲して生きるのだ
And live while desiring discord?
今日も泳いでる 夜の電車が通り去っていく
Swimming again today, the night train passes by
踊り明かせよ
Dance the night away
パッパラパッパラパッパパッパ
Pappara pappara pappa pappa
ナゾナゾ騙して歌いましょう
Let's sing while deceiving with riddles
タッタラタッタラタッタタッタ
Tattara tattara tatta tatta
なぜなぜここが痛むのでしょう
Why does it hurt here?
Song: Phony / Words, Music, Movie: Tsumiki / Mix: Masutaken
散々な日々は変わらないわ
The terrible days don't change
絶望の雨はやまないわ
The rain of despair doesn't stop
さよならも言えぬまま泣いた フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
I cried without being able to say goodbye, phony phony phony
嘘に絡まってるただ
Just entangled in lies
簡単なこともわからないわ
I don't even understand simple things
あたしって何だっけ それすら夜の手に絆されて
What was I again? Even that is fettered by the hand of night
愛のように
Just like love
さよならまたねと呟いた フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
I whispered "goodbye, see you again", phony phony phony
嘘に絡まってるあたしはフォニイ
Entangled in lies, I am a phony
造花だけが知っている 秘密のフォニイ
Only the artificial flowers know the secret phony
Daphne, Ficus, Iris, Maackia, Lythrum, Myrica, Sabia, flos
flos / 作詞・作曲: R Sound Design
flos / Lyrics & Composition: R Sound Design
拝啓 僕の願いよ
Dear my wishes
未来よ 絶え間ない後悔よ
To the future, to the incessant regrets
体感八度五分の夢は
The dream of an 8.5 degree body temperature
やがて散ってしまった
Has eventually scattered away
Daphne, Ficus, Iris, Maackia, Lythrum, Myrica, Sabia
Thymus, Ribes, Abelia, Sedum
Leivisia, Opuntia, Lychnis
拝啓 君の想いは
Dear your feelings
憂いは 巡る感情論は
To the grief, to the revolving emotional theories
拝啓 八十五分の世界に
Dear to the 85% world
囚われたまま
Remaining imprisoned
骨を刺すひび割れた今日は
On this cracked day that pierces the bones
溢れ出した遺細に
In the overflowing remnants
薪をくべて風に乗せて
Adding logs to the fire, riding the wind
荒んだ空を彩る
Coloring the desolate sky
荒んだ日々を丁寧に
Carefully tending to the desolate days
飾った花はすぐに枯れていく
The decorated flowers soon wither away
淀んだ僕が夢から覚めて
The stagnant me wakes up from the dream
縋った意味も無い無い無い
There's no meaning in what I clung to, none, none, none
君が僕にくれた声も色も
The voice and color you gave me
揺るぎない愛情も
The unwavering affection too
二人きりの空に光った星も
The star that shone in the sky with just the two of us
遠に散ってしまった
Has long since scattered away
難儀の線の黒の塀に
On the black wall of the difficult line
季節は彩を添わせて
Letting the seasons add color
熱を帯びて鈍く沈んで
Carrying heat, sinking dully
擦れた街に零れる
Spilling into the worn-out town
荒んだ日々を丁寧に
Carefully tending to the desolate days
飾った先に花が咲くはず
A flower should bloom where it was decorated
憩な君は夢を見たまま
The idle you, while still dreaming
悟った振りで水を注いだ
Poured water with a knowing look
木漏れ日の中に
Amidst the sunlight filtering through trees
柔らかく咲いた
Softly bloomed
花は雲の上で散る
The flower scatters above the clouds
魔法で 夢の先で 揺れている
By magic, at the end of the dream, it's swaying
荒んだ日々を丁寧に
Carefully treating the desolate days
飾った花はすぐに枯れていく
The flowers I decorated with soon wither away
不純な僕は夢から覚めて
Impurely, I wake from my dream
誓った意味もないな ないな ないな
There's no meaning to the oath I made, none, none
虚な日々を丁寧に
Carefully treating the empty days
綴った紙に花を描いた
I drew flowers on the paper I wrote on
不遇な僕ら夢に溢れて
We, the unfortunate ones, overflow with dreams
誓ったはずもなかったことにした
And acted as if the oath we should've made never happened
ダフネ フィクス アイリス マキア ヴィスラム ミミカ サルビア
サイマス ビーベス アベリア セダム フェリシア オクナ リクニス
Daphne, Ficus, Iris, Machia, Viscum, Mimica, Salvia
Thymus, Vibex, Abelia, Sedum, Felicia, Okuna, Lychnis
ダフネ フィクス アイリス マキア ヴィスラム ミミカ サルビア
サイマス ビーベス アベリア セダム フェリシア オクナ リクニス
Daphne, Ficus, Iris, Machia, Viscum, Mimica, Salvia
Thymus, Vibex, Abelia, Sedum, Felicia, Okuna, Lychnis
フロス
Flos
はい、というわけで聞いていただきましたのは、
Yes, so the two songs you just heard were,
フォニイ、そしてフロスの二曲でした。
"Phony" and "Flos".
はあ。えーっと、この後ね続く実は曲、みんな気づいたかな？どうかな？
Haa. Um, did everyone notice something about the songs that follow? I wonder.
なんかちょっと花に関連してる曲が多いような気がしませんか？
Don't you feel like there are many songs related to flowers?
実はこの後の二曲も花に関連する曲になっています。
In fact, the next two songs are also related to flowers.
結構ね、しっとりとした曲なので、
They're quite mellow songs,
みんなもなんかそんな気持ちで聞いてもらえるといいかなと思います。
so I hope everyone can listen to them with that kind of feeling.
それではみんな、聞いてください。
Then everyone, please listen.
よし、頑張って歌います！
Alright, I'll do my best singing!
ドライフラワー
作詞・作曲：優里
Dry Flower
Lyrics/Composition: Yuuri
多分、私じゃなくてよかった
Maybe it was better it wasn't me
余裕のない二人だったし
We were both overwhelmed
気づけば喧嘩ばかりしてさ、ごめんね
Before I knew it, all we did was fight, I'm sorry
ずっと話そうと思っていた
I'd been thinking about talking to you for a long time
きっと私たち合わないね
We're probably not a good match
二人きりしかいない部屋でさ
In the room where it was just the two of us
あなたばかり話していたよね
You were always the one doing all the talking, right?
もし、いつかどこかで会えたら
If we ever meet somewhere someday
今日の事を笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll laugh about today
理由もちゃんと話せないけれど
I can't even explain the reason properly, but
貴方が眠った後に泣くのは嫌
I hate crying after you've fallen asleep
声も顔も不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your awkwardness
全部全部、嫌いじゃないの
I don't hate all of it, any of it
ドライフラワーみたい 君との日々は
Our days together are like dry flowers
きっときっときっときっと 色褪せる
They will surely, surely, surely, surely fade
多分、君じゃなくてよかった
Maybe it was better it wasn't you
もう泣かされることもないし
I won't be made to cry anymore
「私ばかり」なんて言葉もなくなった
The words "It's always me" are gone too
あんなに悲しい別れでも
Even a breakup that sad,
時間が経てば忘れてく
I'll forget it as time passes
新しい人と並ぶ君は
Beside someone new,
ちゃんと上手くやれているのかな
I wonder if you're doing okay
もう顔も見たくないからさ
I don't even want to see your face anymore
変に連絡してこないでほしい
I don't want you to contact me for no reason
都合がいいのは変わってないんだね
You haven't changed how you only think of your own convenience
でも無視できずにまた少し返事
But I couldn't ignore you and replied a little again
声も顔も不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your awkwardness
今も
Even now
嫌いじゃないの
I don't hate you
ドライフラワーみたいに
Just like a dried flower
時間が経てば
As time goes by
きっと きっと
Surely, surely
色褪せる
The colors will fade
月明かりに魔物が揺れる
Monsters sway in the moonlight
きっと私もどうかしている
I must be going crazy, too
暗闇に色彩が浮かぶ
Colors float in the darkness
赤いアイ色が胸の奥
A deep red indigo in my heart
ずっとあなたの名前を呼ぶ
I'll always be calling your name
好きという気持ちまた香る
The feeling of love wafts again
声も 顔も
Your voice, your face
不器用なとこも
And even your awkwardness
全部 全部
Everything, everything
大嫌いだよ
I hate it all
まだ枯れない花を
A flower that hasn't withered yet
君に添えてさ
I'll place it beside you
ずっと ずっと
Forever and ever
抱えてよ
Hold onto it
花に亡霊 / 作詞・作曲：n-buna
Ghost in a Flower / Lyrics & Composition: n-buna
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've already forgotten
夏の木陰に座ったまま
Sitting in the summer shade
アイスを口に放り込んで
Tossing an ice cream into my mouth
風を待っていた
Waiting for the breeze
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've already forgotten
世の中の全部嘘だらけ
Everything in the world is full of lies
本当の価値を二人で
Let's go find the true value
探しに行こうと笑ったこと
The two of us together, that's what we laughed about
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So I don't forget, so it doesn't fade
形に残るものが全てじゃないように
So that things left in physical form aren't everything
言葉をもっと教えて
Tell me more words
夏が来るって教えて
Tell me that summer is coming
僕は描いてる 眼に映ったのは夏の亡霊だ
I'm drawing what I saw in my eyes was a summer ghost
風にスカートが揺れて
My skirt sways in the wind
思い出なんて忘れて
Forget all about the memories
浅い呼吸をする 汗を拭って夏めく
Take shallow breaths, wipe away the sweat, and feel the summer
もう忘れてしまったかな
I wonder if you've already forgotten
夏の木陰に座った頃
The time we sat in the summer shade
遠くの丘から顔出した雲があったじゃないか
There was a cloud peeking out from the distant hill, wasn't there?
君はそれを掴もうとして
You tried to grab it
馬鹿みたいに空を切った手で
With hands that cut through the empty air like an idiot
僕は紙に雲を一つ書いて 笑って握って見せて
I drew a single cloud on paper, smiled, and showed it to you in my hand
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So I don't forget, so it doesn't fade
歴史に残るものが全てじゃないから
Because things left in history aren't everything
今だけ顔も無くして
Lose your face just for now
言葉も全部忘れて
Forget all the words, too
君は笑ってる 夏を待っている僕ら亡霊だ
You're laughing, we're ghosts waiting for summer
心をもっと教えて
Tell me more of your heart
夏の匂いを教えて
Tell me the scent of summer
浅い呼吸をする
Take shallow breaths
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So I don't forget, so it doesn't fade
心に響くものが全てじゃないから
Because things that resonate in the heart aren't everything
言葉をもっと教えて
Tell me more words
さよならだって教えて
Even tell me "goodbye"
今も見るんだよ　夏に咲いている花に亡霊
I still see them now, ghosts in the flowers blooming in summer
言葉じゃなくて時間を
Not words, but time
時間じゃなくて心を
Not time, but a heart
浅い呼吸をする　汗を拭って夏めく
Taking shallow breaths, wiping sweat as summer approaches
夏の匂いがする
It smells like summer
もう忘れてしまったかな　夏の木陰に座ったまま
Have you forgotten by now? Sitting in the shade of a summer tree
アイスを口に放り込んで　風を待っていた
Throwing ice cream into my mouth, waiting for the breeze
はい、ということで、聴いていただきましたのは「ドライフラワー」、そして「花に亡霊」でした！
Alright, so you just heard "Dry Flower" and "Hana ni Bourei"!
はぁー、みんな、どうでした？
Phew, everyone, how was it?
結構ね、こうゆっくりとした、しっとりとした曲なのでね、みんなもちょっと、なんていうのかな...
They're quite slow, mellow songs, so I think everyone might be feeling... what should I say...
エモい、エモい感じの気持ちになったんじゃないかなと思いますが。
...emotional, a bit of an "emo" feeling.
ここからね、ちょっとそのエモい気持ちをテンション上げていってもらいますよ！
From here on, I want you to take that emotional feeling and pump up the energy!
そう、ここからは、なんと重大告知のお時間となっておりまーす！
That's right, from here on, it's time for some major announcements!
ね！重大告知、何だっけ？それ何だっけ？
Right! Major announcements, what were they again? What were they?
どんな告知だと思う？今日の最初にもちょっと言ってたよね。
What kind of announcements do you think they are? I mentioned it a bit at the beginning of today too.
そう！あの、とある水族館とのコラボの詳細です！イエーイ！
Yes! It's the details of the collaboration with a certain aquarium! Yay!
え、100万人記念！100万人登録者記念の、超ビッグなコラボのお知らせです。まずはこちらをご覧ください！
So, 1 million subscribers! It's a notice of a super big collaboration to celebrate reaching 1 million subscribers. First, please take a look at this!
ドン！はい、めちゃめちゃ可愛い！イエイイエイイエイ！
Boom! Yes, it's so incredibly cute! Yay yay yay!
見てください、このチンアナゴが「100」、100万人の「100」をこう形作ってるんですよ。
Look, these garden eels are forming the number "100", for 1 million.
そしてちょっとこのラミィの大胆な衣装...ちょっと恥ずかしいけど、今回ね、100万人ってことでちょっとこの激し、激しめの衣装を着てみました。どうでしょうか、みんな。
And this rather bold outfit for Lamy... it's a bit embarrassing, but since it's for 1 million, I tried wearing this a bit more daring outfit. What do you think, everyone?
記念イラスト、可愛い？
The commemorative illustration, is it cute?
可愛い！可愛いでしょう。可愛いとラミィも思います。
It's cute! It is, right? Lamy thinks so too.
そしてこれだけじゃないんですよ。
And that's not all.
そう、とある水族館、とある水族館についての詳細な告知ですよ。
Yes, a certain aquarium, it's the detailed announcement about that certain aquarium.
まずね、とある水族館ってどこなの？と思ってるみんな。
First of all, to everyone wondering, "where is this certain aquarium?"
それはこちら！
Here it is!
ジャン！あ、これで分かった方いるかな？もう一枚、ドン！
Ta-da! Ah, did anyone recognize it from this? One more, boom!
これは、サンシャイン水族館！東京・池袋にあるサンシャイン水族館さんとのコラボが決定いたしました！イエーイイエイイエイ！
This is Sunshine Aquarium! A collaboration with Sunshine Aquarium in Ikebukuro, Tokyo has been decided! Yay yay yay!
いや、あの、以前ね、Twitterでちょっと告知をさせていただいた時に、「とある水族館とコラボするよ」って言ったら、いや、結構ね、みんな色んな水族館の名前を出してくれて、「どこかな、どこかな」って言って。
Well, when I made a little announcement on Twitter before saying "I'm collaborating with a certain aquarium," everyone was suggesting all sorts of aquarium names, wondering "where could it be?"
で、まず「サンシャイン水族館じゃないかな」って当ててた方もいました。
And there were some who correctly guessed "maybe it's Sunshine Aquarium."
そしてこちらが、ミズクラゲをイメージした今回のキービジュアルとなっております。
And this is the key visual for the collaboration, inspired by moon jellies.
実はね、この後ろがサンシャイン水族館さんの、あのクラゲ空間になってるんですよ。
Actually, the background is the jellyfish area at Sunshine Aquarium.
そう、なのでね、このキービジュアル見て「これはサンシャイン水族館のクラゲ空間だ」って当ててた方もいました。すごすぎる。
That's right, so there were people who saw this key visual and guessed, "This is the jellyfish space at Sunshine Aquarium." That's incredible.
そして、えーと、コラボ期間なんですけれども...
And, um, regarding the collaboration period...
9月8日の木曜日から、9月25日、日曜日の約3週間。3週間となっております。
It will be for about three weeks, from Thursday, September 8th to Sunday, September 25th.
夜間特別営業「サンシャイン水族館 × 雪花ラミィ #アクアラミウム 」を実施いたします。イエーイ！
We will be holding a special nighttime event, "Sunshine Aquarium x Yukihana Lamy #AquaLamyum". Yay!
いや、もうラミィが水族館大好きっていうのはもうデビュー配信から言ってたんだけど。
Well, I've been saying I love aquariums since my debut stream.
ラミィの、あの配信画面の...
Lamy's, you know, the streaming screen's...
...後ろにもね、水族、水族館じゃないや、あの水槽置いて...
...behind it, an aquarium—no, not an aquarium, a tank is placed...
...ミズクラゲをこう流してもらったりとかしてるんだけど...
...and I have moon jellyfish floating in it and such...
...それぐらいで本当に水族館の、特にねクラゲが好きなので...
...that's how much I really love aquariums, especially jellyfish, so...
...本、ほっ、本当にすごいこのコラボが実現して嬉しいでしょう...
...I'm, I'm, I'm really so happy that this amazing collaboration happened...
...もう嬉しい！ありがたい！
...I'm so happy! Thank you!
そして、コラボはまだまだあります。
And, there's even more to the collaboration.
実はね、コラボイラストっていうのがあるので、ちょっと１個ずつみんなに紹介していきたいと思います。こちら！
Actually, we have collaboration illustrations, so I'd like to introduce them to you one by one. Here they are!
はい、こちら、みんなね見て分かると思いますけど、ミズクラゲとラミィです。
Yes, here, as you can probably tell by looking, are Moon Jellyfish and Lamy.
可愛いでしょう。
Aren't they cute?
実はね、今回クラゲはミズクラゲだけじゃないんですよ。
Actually, the jellyfish this time aren't just moon jellyfish.
もう一個！こちら！
One more! This one!
これみんな分かるかな？これ何のクラゲか分かりますか？
Do you all know this one? Do you know what kind of jellyfish this is?
ブルージェリーです。
It's a blue jelly.
このね、ブルージェリーも、サンシャイン水族館のクラゲ空間にいるので、ぜひぜひみんなね、こう実物も見てほしいと思います。
This blue jelly is also in the jellyfish space at Sunshine Aquarium, so I definitely want everyone to see the real thing.
すごいね、きれいで可愛いクラゲです。
It's a very beautiful and cute jellyfish.
そして、もう一つ。ドン！
And one more. Bam!
これコツメカワウソ、可愛いでしょう。
This is a small-clawed otter, isn't it cute?
頭の上にね、乗っかってるんですよ、コツメカワウソが。
The otter is sitting right on top of my head.
いや、これね実物も本当に可愛いの。
Well, the real ones are really cute too.
すっごい可愛いからみんなで見に行ってほしい。ほんっっとうに可愛いの。
They're so cute, so I want everyone to go see them. They're really, really cute.
そして、こちら。
And this one.
ケープペンギン×雪民さん。雪民さんこんなところでケープペンギンの、なんかケープをかぶってる。
Cape Penguin x Yukimin. Yukimin is here, wearing a Cape penguin cape.
ケープペンギン。
Cape Penguin.
いやこれ何でもない、何でもない。可愛いでしょう。
No, it's nothing, it's nothing. Isn't it cute?
そして最後にこちら。
And finally, this one.
えーとみんな知ってるかな？このお魚。キッシンググラミーっていうねお魚なんだけど...
Um, does everyone know this fish? It's a fish called a Kissing Gourami...
...キッシング。チュッチュッチュ。チュッをねするねお魚なんですよ。
...Kissing. Chu-chu-chu. It's a fish that kisses.
ラミィもね、みんなによくさ、んまんまんまんまってチュウするでしょう？んまんまんまんまって。
Lamy also often gives you all kisses like "muah muah muah," right? Like "muah muah muah."
キッシンググラミー、キッシンググラミー、キッシンググラミー、キッシンググラミー、キッシンググラミー。
Kissing Gourami, Kissing Gourami, Kissing Gourami, Kissing Gourami, Kissing Gourami.
いやもうこれは、もうシナジー、シナジーです。
Well, this is just—it's synergy, synergy.
ということで、えーこちらのね、今紹介したイラストはコラボグッズとして、みんなの手元にも入手可能になっております。
So, these illustrations I just introduced will be available to you all as collaboration goods.
えー他にもね、実はね、あの夏の終わりでもまだちょっと暑いかなと思って、ちょっとねそういう感じのコラボグッズいろいろあるんですよ。
And actually, there are various other collab goods like that, since I thought it might still be a bit hot at the end of summer.
ちょっとね、今日はおすすめ、おすすめとかね、ちょっと紹介したかったんだけど時間がないので...
I wanted to recommend and introduce some today, but we're short on time...
えーと、今度ね、えー公開されるEC限定の、おもちゃ、おもちゃじゃないや、一部現地...
so, the EC-exclusive items that will be released... not toys, but some local...
...限定のグッズとか、EC限定の商品とかもあるので、後日公開させ、ろ、ろ、ろ...
...limited goods and EC-exclusive products are available, so...
...後日公開される特設サイトがある、サイトがあるので、そこをチェックしてみてください。噛み噛みだよ、噛み噛み。
...there's a special site that will be released later, so please check it out. I'm so tongue-tied, so tongue-tied.
まだ歌あるのに、どうしよう。
I still have songs to sing, what should I do?
えーそしてですね、こちらのグッズ、えーサンシャイン水族館にて９月８日の木曜日から、９月２５日日曜日のコラボ開催期間中...
And these goods will be available at Sunshine Aquarium during the collaboration period from Thursday, September 8th, to Sunday, September 25th...
...ECサイトでは、９月１５日の木曜日から、１０月２日の日曜日の期間に入手することができます。
...and on the EC site from Thursday, September 15th, to Sunday, October 2nd.
えーそしてですね、そのほか、水族館内では書き下ろしのイラストを使用したフォトスポットが設置されてたり...
And also, there will be photo spots using newly drawn illustrations set up in the aquarium...
...現地でしか体験できない、これちょっと有料になっちゃうんですけど、音声ガイドが聞けたりとか。
...and you can listen to an audio guide, which is exclusive to the site and costs a bit extra.
さらに、水族館内にタリーズさんがあるんですけど、このタリーズさんでもコラボドリンクとフードが売っていたりとか。
Furthermore, there's a Tully's in the aquarium, and they'll be selling collaboration drinks and food too.
もうとにかく、サンシャイン水族館がラミィで溢れた状態になっています。
In any case, Sunshine Aquarium will be overflowing with Lamy.
いやもうね、ぜひぜひ雪民さん、遊びに行ってみてください。
So, Yukimin, please come and visit.
えーそして、この、このイベントなんですけど、えー水族館の通常営業終了後に開催される夜間限定のイベントになっているので...
And as for this event, it's a night-only event held after the aquarium's regular business hours...
...えー来場前にチケットや時間などは特設サイトでよく確認するようにしてください。
...so please be sure to check the special website for tickets and times before coming.
ふぅー、噛み噛みだなぁ。
Phew, I'm so tongue-tied.
今日はいっぱい踊って歌ってとかしてたからね、もう口の中がお疲れになってきてしまっているという。
I've been dancing and singing a lot today, so my mouth is getting tired.
あ、ちなみに、なんですけど、この水族館内にあるタリーズさんで...
Oh, by the way, at the Tully's in the aquarium...
...開催される
...will be held.
あのコラボドリンクとかフードっていうのは、
Those collab drinks and food items,
今現在絶賛開発中となっております。
are currently under intensive development.
えー、もうね、これね、ちょっとみんな楽しみにしててくださーい。
Um, everyone, please look forward to this!
そして、詳細なんですけど、
And as for the details,
なんと3日後、3日後、
unbelievably, 3 days from now, 3 days from now,
8月15日に公開される特設ページ、
on August 15th, a special page will be released.
これがね、公開されましたら、
Once it's released,
Twitterとかできちんとみんなにお知らせしますので、
I'll inform everyone properly on Twitter and such,
ラミィのTwitterをフォローして、通知もオンにしておいてください。
so please follow Lamy's Twitter and turn on notifications.
以上、重大お知らせでしたー！イェーイ！
That's all for the major announcements! Yay!
や、みんなすごいでしょ、驚いたでしょ？
Wow, everyone, isn't it great? You were surprised, right?
ちょっとさ、今、情報量が多すぎて、
Right now, there's so much information,
みんなの頭が追いついてないかもしれないけど、大丈夫かな？
that your heads might not be keeping up, but are you okay?
そうなんです。
That's right.
今までね、匂わせに匂わせてきた水族館は、
The aquarium I've been hinting at all this time,
サンシャイン水族館さんとの、
was with Sunshine Aquarium,
う、サンシャイン水族館さんとの大型コラボでした。
er, a large-scale collaboration with Sunshine Aquarium.
ということで、まだまだ
So, it's far,
まだまだ雪花ラミィのセカンドアニバーサリーライブは続きます。
far from over, Yukihana Lamy's 2nd Anniversary Live.
この後は、みんなが大好きな、
After this, a song everyone loves,
そしてラミィが大好きな、
and that I love,
あの曲を歌っていこうと思います。
I'm going to sing that song.
なんだか分かる？ほら、あの...
Do you know what it is? You know, that...
雪が...
Snow...
降る...
falls...
スノーな...
snowy...
あはは！もうここまで言えば分かったかなと思うので、
Ahaha! I think you've figured it out by now since I've said this much.
それではね、ちょっと衣装チェンジをしたりとかもするので、
Well then, I'm going to change my outfit and such,
準備してきますので、みんな待っててね。
so I'll get ready. Everyone, please wait.
それじゃ、いってきまーす。
Alright, here I go!
ま、ま、ま、ま、ま、ま、キッシングラミィ、キッシングラミィ、キッシングラミィ、キッシングラミィ。
Ma, ma... Kissing Lamy, Kissing Lamy, Kissing Lamy, Kissing Lamy.
Snow halation
不思議だね 今の気持ち
It's strange, isn't it? These feelings now
空から降ってきたみたい
It's as if they fell from the sky
特別な季節の色が
The colors of this special season
ときめきを見せるよ
Show me the excitement
初めて出会った時から
From the moment we first met
予感に騒ぐ
My premonition was restless
心のメロディ
The melody of my heart
とめられない とまらない なぜ
I can't stop it, I can't stop it, why?
届けて 切なさには
Deliver it! To this heartache...
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
...shall we give it a name? "Snow halation"
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap
待てずに悔しいけど 好きって純情
I can't wait, it's frustrating, but love is pure
微熱の中 ためらってもダメダメ
In this slight fever, hesitating is no-no
飛び込む勇気に賛成 まもなくStart!!
I agree with the courage to dive in, it's about to Start!!
音もなく気配もなく
Without a sound, without a trace
静かに運命は変わる
Destiny silently changes
これからの未来に胸の
In the future to come, my heart's...
鼓動が早くなる
...beat quickens.
例えば困った時には
For example, when you're in trouble
すぐ駆けつけて
I'll come running immediately
抱きしめたくて
Wanting to hold you
どこにいてもどこまでも Fly high
No matter where you are, no matter how far, Fly high
急いで いつつのまにか
Hurry, before I knew it...
大きくなりすぎた “True emotion”
...it's grown too big, "True emotion"
夢だけ見てるようじゃ
Just looking at dreams...
つらいよ 恋人は君って言いたい
...is painful, I want to say you're my lover.
優しい目が とまどってる 嫌だよ
Your kind eyes are bewildered, I hate it.
このまま一気に愛情 あずけて Please!!
Just like that, all at once, entrust your affection, Please!!
届けて 切なさには
Deliver it, for the sadness...
名前をつけようか Snow halation
Let's give it a name: Snow halation.
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap...
待てずに 悔しいけど 好きって純情
I can't wait, it's frustrating, but love is pure.
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, it's no good to hesitate.
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I'm for the courage to dive in.
まもなく Start!!
It's starting soon!!
ということで、聞いていただきました『Snow halation』でした！
And so, that was "Snow halation"!
実はですね、この後、雪花ラミィ
Actually, after this, Lamy Yukihana...
2曲目のオリジナル曲を最後にみんなに聴いていただこうと思うんですけど
...is going to have everyone listen to her second original song as the finale.
今回、この『Snow halation』の作詞作曲をね、されている山田高弘先生に、
For this one, Takahiro Yamada, who composed "Snow halation,"
今回ね、作曲・編曲していただきまして
handled the composition and arrangement this time.
作詞はNekohackerさんにお願いしていただきました。
And I had Nekohacker handle the lyrics.
そして曲名は、今回のこちらのタイトルにもなってる
And the song title is the same as the title for this live,
『Fleur』、こちらが2曲目のタイトルになってます。
"Fleur." That's the title of the second song.
そしてですね、今回、2周年のオリジナル記念グッズなんですが、
And now, regarding the 2nd anniversary original commemorative goods,
その2曲目のオリ曲にちなんだグッズがたくさん出ているのでちょっと見ていきましょう！ドン！
there are many items related to that second original song, so let's take a look! Boom!
活動2周年記念
2nd Anniversary Commemoration
はい！雪花ラミィ活動2周年記念。
Yes! Lamy Yukihana 2nd Anniversary.
8月12日、え、9時から、この後9時から発売開始します！
Sales start at 9 PM on August 12th!
それでは一個ずつ紹介していきたいと思います！
So, I'd like to introduce them one by one!
じゃん！えっとね、あ、そう。今日は大福がいるんですよ。大福がいるから、ちょっとみんな待っててね。
Ta-da! And, oh, right. Daifuku is here today. Daifuku is here, so everyone, please wait a moment.
ほら、大福だよ！ということで、大福と一緒に紹介していきたいと思います！
Look, it's Daifuku! So, I'll introduce them together with Daifuku!
まず、このアクリルスタンド。アクリルスタンド見えてるかな？
First, this acrylic stand. Can you see the acrylic stand?
こちらリン☆ユウ先生が新曲のMVのイメージに合わせて
This is an acrylic stand newly illustrated by Rin Yuu-sensei
描き下ろしで作っていただきましたアクリルスタンドとなっております。
to match the theme of the new song's music video.
ちょっとね、おしゃれな形になってるんですよ。
It has a bit of a stylish design.
丸い感じの球体に入った……おっ！球体に入った感じで、
It's inside a round sphere... Oh! Inside the sphere,
小さい大福と雪民さんもいるんですよ。すごいでしょ、これ。綺麗でしょ。
there's also a tiny Daifuku and a Yukimin. Isn't it great? It's beautiful.
そして次がこちら。藤ちょこ先生に描き下ろしで書いていただきました、
And next is this. Newly illustrated by Fuji Choko-sensei,
こちらも新曲のMVのイメージに合わせたキャンバスボードとなっております。
this is also a canvas board matching the theme of the new song's music video.
あの、キャンバスボードなので結構飾るのにすごいいい感じの
Since it's a canvas board, it's a very nice,
インテリアなおしゃれな感じのキャンバスボードになってます。
stylish interior piece for decorating.
そして次がこちら。等身大雪民ぬいぐるみ！
And next is this. A life-size Yukimin plushie!
これみんな待ってたんじゃないでしょうか。あのね、過去に等身大大福ぬいぐるみっていうのはあったんですけど、
I bet you've all been waiting for this. You know, we had a life-size Daifuku plushie in the past,
ついに満を持して雪民さんのぬいぐるみが登場しました！
but finally, the Yukimin plushie has arrived!
雪民さんが雪民さんを抱きしめる、そんなよく分からない構図をぜひぜひ皆さん作ってください。
Please create that mysterious scene where a Yukimin hugs a Yukimin.
大体ね、大きさは18cm×18cmの、こう丸い感じのサイズになっております。
The size is roughly 18cm by 18cm, a nice round shape.
ちょっとね、細かいサイズはこの後サイトの方見ていただければと思います。
For more details on the size, please check the website later.
めちゃめちゃ可愛い。ふわふわでね、すごい可愛いです。
It's incredibly cute. It's soft and really adorable.
そしてこちら。雪民証明書！
And here's this. A Yukimin certificate!
こういうの今まで一回も作ったことなくて。
I've never made anything like this before.
まあ持ってなくてももちろん雪民さんなんだけど、持ってると雪民ですという証明がすぐできるというものになっております。
Of course, you're still a Yukimin even if you don't have one, but with this, you can immediately prove you're a Yukimin.
...となっております。
...is what it is.
なんかね、どこかでほら、みんなでこう、雪民さん同士あった時に、
You know, if you happen to run into another Yukimin somewhere,
これを見せ合うことで、「むむ、お前も雪民か」というのがね、すぐわかるっていうね。
you can show this to each other and immediately know, "Oh, you're a Yukimin too!"
そんなことするかどうか分かんないけど、え、雪民証明書となっております。
I don't know if anyone will actually do that, but yes, this is the Yukimin Certificate.
そして最後に、フルセット購入特典といたしまして、
And finally, as a bonus for purchasing the full set,
リンユウ先生の描き下ろしのポストカード、こちらがですね、今回、
there's a postcard illustrated by Rin Yuu-sensei, and this time,
スクエアになっているので、いつものね、あのサイズよりもね、
it's square-shaped, so compared to the usual size,
ちょっと小さめの可愛い感じのサイズになっております。
it's a bit smaller and has a cute feel to it.
これに、箔押しの複製サインと、え、
This will include a foil-stamped copy of my signature and,
箔押しの、え、複製メッセージを入れて、
a foil-stamped copy of my message,
皆様に、え、フルセットをね、購入していただいた方にお届けする形になっております。
which we will deliver to everyone who purchased the full set.
何が書いてあるかは、え、届くまでのお楽しみ、ということで。
As for what's written on it, please look forward to finding out when it arrives.
ということで、それではね、最後の
All right then, let's head into
オリ曲、いきましょう！
the final original song!
サイリウムは待っててね！
Get your penlights ready!
じゃあみんな、
Well then, everyone,
行ってきまーす！
here I go!
Fleur
雪が降り この夜を
Snow falls, and through this night,
月明かりが照らしてく
the moonlight illuminates everything.
好きなフリとかじゃない 本当の気持ちに
It's not just pretending to like you; these real feelings,
初めて気がついた
I've realized them for the first time.
はじまりはいつだって
Beginnings are always
突然のStory
a sudden story.
キミのことを考えるだけで
Just by thinking of you,
想い 溢れてく
my feelings overflow.
雪が煌めくこの花束
This bouquet where snow sparkles,
抱えて祈ってる キミに渡せるように
I hold it and pray, so that I can give it to you.
指先が震えるまでかな
Until my fingertips tremble,
待ってるね いつだって
I'll be waiting, always,
この想い
to let these feelings
届けよう
reach you.
意味もなく過ごしてた
I had been spending my days meaninglessly,
日々を変えてくれたから
but you changed them for me.
キミも泣くことぐらいあるよねってそっと
I want to gently stay by your side,
寄り添ってあげたいな
thinking that you must have times when you cry too.
終わらないでと願う 大切なMoment
This precious moment I pray won't end.
知りたいでも知りたくはないの
I want to know, but I don't want to know,
ここに閉じ込めて
lock it all up in here.
ああ
Ah...
たったひとつだけのわがまま
Please grant me just this one selfish wish:
叶えてくれるかな 一番にしてよね
Make me your number one.
運命と呼ぶにはまだまだ
It's still not enough
足りない でもずっと
to call it destiny, but always,
キミだけを
I'll be looking
見てるよ
at only you.
雪が煌めくこの花束
This bouquet where snow sparkles,
抱えて祈ってる キミに渡せるように
I hold it and pray, so that I can give it to you.
指先が震えるまでかな
Until my fingertips tremble...
ちょっと まだまだ
Wait, there's still more
待ってるね
I'll be waiting
いつだって
Always
この想い
These feelings
届けよう
Let's send them out
好きだよ
I love you
2nd Anniversary! ♡
雪民さんがいたから、今日のラミィがいて、明日のラミィもいるよ♡
Because the Yukimin were there, today's Lamy exists, and tomorrow's Lamy will too♡
3年目も、みんなと一緒に色んな景色を見ていきたい！！
In the third year too, I want to see many different sights together with everyone!!
いつも本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much as always!
大好きだよ♡ んまんまちゅ
I love you♡ *Mwah*